blogs911.com 2014-11-02

# Privacy Policy | BloGs911

**What do we use your information for?**   
  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
  
To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.  
  **Online Privacy Policy Only**   
  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  
  
**Your Consent**   
  
By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).  
  
**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   
  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.   
  
**Contacting Us**   
  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
